Alumni Association; Records ua801
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Class Notes and Communication, 1859-2011; Undated; 4; 4.52 cubic ft.
  - Class of 1912 and 1913 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 70)
  - Class of 1922 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 71)
  - Tax Card Mailings, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 72)
  - Class of 1937 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1974; 1976; 1992 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 73)
  - Class of 1972 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1975; 1978 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 74)
  - Class of 1935 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1976; 1985; 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 75)
  - Class of 1967 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1992 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 76)
  - Class of 1950 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972-1996 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 77)
  - Rochester Chapter, 1972; 1974; 1985 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 78)
  - Class of 1928 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972; 1976; 1993 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 79)
  - Class of 1956 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 80)
  - Class of 1957 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972; 1977 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 81)
  - Class of 1942 Newsletters and Reunions, 1972; 1992; 2002; 2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 82)
  - Carillon Special Issue, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 83)
  - Class of 1923 Newsletters and Reunions, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 84)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 85)
  - General Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1948 Newsletters and Reunions, 1973-2011 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 2)
  - Class of 1953 Newsletters and Reunions, 1973; 1993 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 3)
  - Class of 1943 Newsletters and Reunions, ca. 1973; 1978; 1992-1993; 2011 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 4)
  - Class of 1933 Newsletters and Reunions, ca. 1973; 1992-1993 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 5)
  - Class of 1959 Newsletters and Reunions, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 6)
  - Class of 1964 Newsletters and Reunions, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 7)
  - Theta Xi Omega, 1974-1975; 1978 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 8)
  - Potter Club Alumni, 1974-1976; 1978 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 9)
  - Class of 1930 Newsletters and Reunions, 1974-1975; 1979; 1992 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 10)
  - Alpha Pi Alpha, 1974-1976 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 11)
  - Class of 1973 Newsletters and Reunions, 1974-1976 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 12)
  - Kappa Delta, 1974; 1976 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 13)
  - Western New York Branch, 1974-1979; 1983-1985 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 14)
  - Class of 1934 Newsletters and Reunions, 1974; 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 15)
  - Psi Gamma, 1974; 1976; 1979; Undated (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 16)
  - Development at Albany Speech, 1975 October 02 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 17)
  - Albany Almanac, 1975; 1978-1979; 1982 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 18)
  - Class of 1925 Newsletters and Reunions, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 19)
  - Emergency Class Letter to Classes of 1969-1973 Regarding State Budget, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 20)
  - Faculty Reunion, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 21)
  - Half Century Club, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 22)
  - Myskania, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 23)
  - Class of 1974 Newsletters and Reunions, 1975-1976; 1979 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 24)
  - Class of 1916 Newsletters and Reunions, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 25)
  - Class of 1919 Newsletters and Reunions, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 26)
  - Delta Sigma Pi, 1976; 1978; Undated (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 27)
  - Class of 1975 Newsletters and Reunions, 1976; 1979 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 28)
  - Stewardship Report, 1977-1999; Undated (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 29)
  - Homecoming, 1978 (Box 4 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 30)
  - School of Library and Information Science, 1978 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1978-1982; Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 2)
  - Class of 1976 Newsletters and Reunions, 1978; 1991 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 3)
  - Class of 1977 Newsletters and Reunions, 1978; ca. 1992 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 4)
  - Phi Delta, 1980 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 5)
  - Pep Band, 1980; Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 6)
  - Capital District Branch, 1980; 1982-1985; 2003 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 7)
  - 2nd circle Club, 1982; 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 8)
  - Half Century Club, 1982; 19865 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 9)
  - Mohawk Valley Branch, 19832-1984 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 10)
  - College House, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 11)
  - Carillon All Star, 1984 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 12)
  - "We're On Our Way to You" Marketing Materials, 1984 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 13)
  - Adirondack Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 14)
  - Binghamton Area, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 15)
  - Boston Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 16)
  - Gold Coast Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 17)
  - Greater Syracuse Area Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 18)
  - "Keep in Touch" Mailer, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 19)
  - Poughkeepsie Area Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 20)
  - West Central Florida Alumni Club, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 21)
  - Class of 1986 Pledge Program, ca. 1986 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 22)
  - Class of 1936 Newsletters and Reunions, 1986-1997 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 23)
  - The Carillon, 1987-1991 (Oversized 9)
  - Class of 1981 Newsletters and Reunions, 1991 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 24)
  - Class of 1931 Newsletters and Reunions, ca. 1991 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 25)
  - Class of 1987 Newsletters and Reunions, ca. 1992 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 26)
  - Class of 1938 Newsletters and Reunions, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 27)
  - Class of 1958 Newsletters and Reunions, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 28)
  - Class of 1978 Newsletters and Reunions, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 29)
  - Class of 1983 Newsletters and Reunions, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 30)
  - Class Notes Pages from the Carillon, 1996 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 31)
  - Class of 1936 Newsletters and Reunions, 2001; Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 32)
  - Middle Earth Reunion, 2010 (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 33)
  - Alumni Mailing Notes, Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 34)
  - Classes 1978-1985, Young Alumni, Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 35)
  - Freshman Focus '88, Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 36)
  - List of Missing Alumni Quarterlies, Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 37)
  - Locating Alumni Cards, Undated (Box 5 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 38)
- Buildings and Construction, 1921-1996; Undated; 5; 2.38 cubic ft.
  This series consists of Alumni Association records related to building dormitories for students and the Alumni House Conference Center. Beginning in 1921 the Alumni Association created a Dormitory Committee/Residence Hall Building Fund with the goal of raising funds to purchase land and build dormitories, especially for women. In 1921 the College's only residential building was Syddum Hall, housing 29 female students. The great majority of students commuted from home, lived in boarding houses throughout the City of Albany, fraternity or sorority houses or at the YWCA. In 1935 Pierce Hall opened to house female students and in 1941, Sayles Hall opened for men.
  Many files in this series document this decades-long endeavor to build more college dormitories and include committee minutes, reports, correspondence, lists of pledges by classes, newsclippings and outreach materials designed to secure financial commitment from alumni, students and the community in the funding drive. Professor John Sayles, future College president, and Dr. Erastus Corning, a member of the college board of trustees, served successive terms as chairs of the Dormitory Committee in the 1920s. The City of Albany and its citizens also pledged its support and dollars.
  Of interest to researchers will be the pamphlets and other outreach materials created to encourage fund-raising among the various constituencies. An editorial in the Alumni Quarterly written by a member of the Class of 1920 compares the "meager equipment" and "impossible housing conditions" of State to Vassar College. Pamphlets for district chairmen of the fund-raising campaign liken it to a machine that must be embolden and put into motion. A newsclipping from 1922 notes how members of the Eta Phi sorority will walk home from college that year and instead pledge the money earmarked for their train fares home to the dormitory fund.
  Please see Series 6, Benevolent Association, for additional files related to the acquisition of land for residence halls and operation of the dormitories. The Benevolent Association, incorporated in 1926, managed the campus residence halls until 1967.
  The series also contains records which document the construction of Alumni House, begun in 1974, and its subsequent use as a conference center on campus and gathering point for alumni. Like the dormitory effort, the Alumni Association formed an Alumni House Building Committee in 1972 and the series contains files on the Committee, correspondence, construction plans, photographs, and event materials.
  Please see the related Alumni Memorabilia Collection for Anna Pierce's materials from the Class of 1884 and Marialla Conklin Whitbeck's files from the Class of 1899, both of which contain additional information about campus buildings and dormitories.
  - Syddum Hall Information: Correspondence between Anna E. Pierce and Miss Van Liew, 1921-1922 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 1)
  - Residence Hall Building Fund, 1921-1923; Undated (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 2)
  - Resolution, Trustee Approval of Dormitory Facilities, ca. 1921 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 3)
  - Outline of Report of the Residence Hall Committee to Date, 1922 August 04 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 4)
  - Historical Outline of Dormitory Drive, ca. 1922 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 5)
  - Residence Hall Campaign Committee Scrapbook, ca. 1922 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 6)
  - Residence Hall Committee Correspondence, 1922-1923; 1925; Undated (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 7)
  - Day Book, Residence Hall Fund, Alumni Association, 1922-1925 (Oversized 10)
  - Residence Hall Committee Minutes, 1922-1928 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 8)
  - Residence Hall Campaign Committee, 1924-1925 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 9)
  - Report of Residence Hall Funds, 1925 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 10)
  - Pierce, Anna E. - Plans for a Residence Hall, 1925 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 11)
  - Residence Hall Fund New Campaign, 1925-1930 (Oversized 10)
  - Residence Hall Fund: Pledges by Classes, 1926 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 12-13)
  - Residence Hall Fund, Also Special Gifts (Furnishing Roome, etc.) in Back of Journal, 1930-1940 (Oversized 10)
  - History and News of Residence Halls, 1934-1966 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 14)
  - Pierce Hall, 1934 September-1936 November (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 15)
  - State and Alumni Residence Halls, Announcements of Rooming and Boarding, 1936-1952 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 16)
  - Residence Halls, Holding Corporation Minutes, 1936 October-1954 April (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 17)
  - Residence Halls Holding Corporation Correspondence, 1937 December-1942 March; Undated (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 18)
  - Residence Halls Financial Statements, 1937-1948 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 19)
  - Residence Hall Fund, 1940-1949 (Oversized 3)
  - Residence Halls Building Fund Journal, 1941-1959 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 21)
  - Sayles Hall, 1941 April-1942 January (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 22)
  - The Ceremony of the Dedication of Sayles Hall- Program, donated by Mrs. Edward Greene, Class of 1946, 1941 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 23)
  - Invitation to the Laying of the Cornerstone of the Men's Residence Hall, donated by Mrs. Edward Greene, Class of 1946, 1941 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 24)
  - Alumni Residence Hall, Pierce Hall, Book of Hospitality, 1943-1958 (Oversized 10)
  - Van Derzee Hall, 1956 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 25)
  - Uptown Construction, 1963 October 11 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 26)
  - Carillon Tower Under Construction Photograph, 1966 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 27)
  - Uptown Campus Construction Photograph, 1966 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 28)
  - Aerial View of the Entire Uptown Campus- Photograph, 1960s (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 29)
  - Alumni House Conference Center Prospectus, 1972 December 11 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 30)
  - Alumni House Conference Center Profile, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 31)
  - Building Committee, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 32)
  - Richard G. Jaques Associates Architects-including Layout Plans, 1973-1976 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 33-34)
  - Alumni House Building Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 35-36)
  - Conference Center, 1973-1984 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 37)
  - Invitation to Ground Breaking Ceremony, Alumni House, 1974 May 18 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 38)
  - Alumni House Conference Center Construction Program Booklet, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 39)
  - Alumni House - Lease for Land, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 40)
  - Alumni House, Solar Collector, 1974-1983; Undated (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 41-42)
  - Alumni House Construction Photographs, 1975 August (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 43)
  - Article on Campus Architecture, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 44)
  - Building Committee for Alumni House, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 1)
  - Alumni House Contractor - Reimheer & Schmidt, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 2)
  - Alumni House Equipment, 1975-1980; Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 3)
  - Alumni House Trees, 1976-1979 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 4)
  - Alumni House Furnishings, 1976-1982 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 5)
  - Alumni House Kitchen, 1976-1991 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 6)
  - Alumni House Completed Events, 1977 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 7-8)
  - Alumni House Conference Center, 1977-1986 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 9-10)
  - Agenda for New York State, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 11)
  - Alumni House Complete Events (including Helios Conference), 1978 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 12-14)
  - Alumni House Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 15)
  - Alumni House Maintenance, 1978; 1983; 1996 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 16)
  - Alumni House Blueprints, 1979 August 02 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 17)
  - Alumni House 3rd Anniversary -"Director's Corner", 1979 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 18)
  - Alumni House Donors Plaque, 1981 August 21 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 19)
  - Alumni House Photographs, 1982; Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 20)
  - Alumni House Elevator Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 21)
  - Alumni House Paintings, 1991 August 22 (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 22)
  - Alumni House Conference Center Construction Program, Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 23)
  - Alumni House Dedication, Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 24)
  - Alumni House Development, including Memos, Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 25-26)
  - Uptown Campus Photographs, including Carillon, Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 27)
  - Willett Street Building, Undated (Box 2 (5-Buildings and Construction), Folder 28)
- Benevolent Association, 1926-1979; Undated; 6; 0.4 cubic ft.
  The Benevolent Association of the New York State College for Teachers was incorporated in 1926 and its Board of Directors first met in Albany in August 1927. While the organization's constitution stresses that its main purpose is to "heighten and enrich the physical, mental, social and moral life of the students," the Benevolent Association was closely connected to the Alumni Association and an outgrowth of the original Dormitory/Residence Hall Building Committee. The Benevolent Association acquired property for dormitories and operated the College (and later University) resident halls until 1967 when they were sold to the State of New York. The Alumni Association also helped nominate the Benevolent Association Board which carried out the policies and recommendations of the Alumni Association. Both groups held their annual meetings at approximately same time.
  In addition to management of the residence halls, the Benevolent Association administered and bequeathed scholarship funds and supported key University projects. In 1982 the Benevolent Association merged with the University Foundation and Annual Fund of the Alumni Association to become the University at Albany Fund, Inc., the central fund-raising arm of the University.
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1926 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1927; Undated (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 2)
  - Board of Director's Meetings, 1927; 1962; 1965 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1937 June-1944 August (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 4)
  - Income Statement, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 5)
  - Personnel Registration, 1962 February 12 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 6)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1963 August-1976 January (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 7)
  - Scholarships, 1964 March-1977 July (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 8-10)
  - Charitable Organization Annual Report, 1964 September-1977 March (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 11-12)
  - Report and Alumni Day Pamphlet, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 13)
  - Committee Members, 1966 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1966; 1968 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 15)
  - Proposal for the Admission and Special Treatment of Underprivileged Students, 1968; Undated (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 16)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 17)
  - History, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 18)
  - Minutes, 1978 June 28 (Box 1 (6-Benevolent Association), Folder 19)
- Theatre Alumni Association, 1932-1974; Undated; 7; 1.03 cubic ft.
  The Theatre Alumni Association of the New York State College for Teachers formed in 1932 to bring alumni together through dramatics and debating. Initially, members were required to have been part of the advanced dramatics class in college, must have taken part in sufficient plays to satisfy the membership committee or have participated in at least two intercollegiate debates. However there are no subsequent records of this group and in June 1954 alumni of State College proposed an organization of former dramatics student to allow alumni greater opportunity for continued participation in the College's theatre activities. The Theatre Alumni Association officially requested affiliation with the Alumni Association of the State University of New York at Albany in 1963. The Theatre Alumni Association dissolved in 1974 with the goal of forming a new organization that brought together faculty, alumni and students in the Theatre Department.
  The records in this series contain the 1932 organization's constitution, the 1954 organization's list of objectives, a revised 1963 constitution and by-laws, executive committee minutes and reports, a scrapbook with clippings about College theatre performances, correspondence, newsletters and membership lists. The group held an annual meeting and party and there are many files detailing events held and awards created to honor Agnes Futterer, member of the Class of 1916 and professor of speech and drama at the College from 1917-1959. In 1957 the first Agnes E. Futterer Award was given on Alumni Day to a graduating student making valuable contributions in dramatics.
  - Constitution, 1932 May 28 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 1)
  - Proposed Organization of Theatre Alumni Association, 1954 June 12 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, General, 1955-1968 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 3)
  - Annual Meetings, 1955-1969 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 4)
  - Membership Lists, 1955-1970 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 5)
  - Futterer Drama Award, 1955-1973 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 6)
  - Committee Memberships, 1956-1963 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1957-1971 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's report, 1957-1971 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 9)
  - General Notes, 1958-1970 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 10)
  - Futterer, Agnes E., 1959 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1959-1973 (Oversized 11)
  - Futterer Recordings-Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 12)
  - "Ghosts", Souvenir Program, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 13)
  - TAA-TLER Newsletter, 1961-1974 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 14)